[
    {
        "front": "ひと",
        "back": "人 \nPerson",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひとり",
        "back": "一人 \nOne person",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんにん",
        "back": "三人 \nThree people",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんじん",
        "back": "日本人 \nJapanese",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "こども",
        "back": "子ども \nChild",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "じょし",
        "back": "女子 \nFemale",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんなのひと",
        "back": "女の人 \nWoman",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんなのこ",
        "back": "女の子 \nGirl",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとこのこ",
        "back": "男の子 \nBoy",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "だんじょ",
        "back": "男女 \nMan and woman",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "め",
        "back": "目 \neye",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちにちめ",
        "back": "一日目 \nThe first day",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "くち",
        "back": "口 \nMouth",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "いりぐち",
        "back": "入口 \nEntrance",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "みみ",
        "back": "耳 \nEar",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "て",
        "back": "手 \nHand",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "じょうずな",
        "back": "上手な \nSkillful",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "へたな",
        "back": "下手な \nUnskillful",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あし",
        "back": "足 \nLeg",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちから",
        "back": "力 \nPower",
        "chapter": "N5 K4"
    }
]